[{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Throughput?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Error_Rate?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Jitter?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Latency?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Interplay_Factors?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Bandwidth?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"bw","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Congession?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Computer_Networks?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"sec","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"scope","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"n1","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Security?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"availabilty","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"modi","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"confid","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"integ","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"interrr","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"sec","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Scope?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"s1","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"s2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"s3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"s4","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"scope","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"PPTP is a subClass from Virtual_Private_Network","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Intrusion_Detection_System is a subClass from Virtual_Private_Network","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Star_Ring","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Star_Mesh is a subClass from Star_Ring","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"NCP is a subClass from Session","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"ISO_Standard is a subClass from Session","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Application","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Network is a subClass from Application","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Media_Access_Control_Sublayer is a subClass from Data_Link","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Presentation is a subClass from Data_Link","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Connection_Control is a subClass from Transport","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Physical is a subClass from Transport","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Tree","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Star is a subClass from Tree","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Ring","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Point_to_Point is a subClass from Ring","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Fully_Connected is a subClass from Mesh","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Hybrid is a subClass from Mesh","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Dairy_Chairs","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Bus is a subClass from Dairy_Chairs","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from X.25","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Fram_Relay is a subClass from X.25","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Key_Loggers","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Zombie is a subClass from Key_Loggers","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Metamorphic is a subClass from Worm","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Exploits is a subClass from Worm","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Downloaders","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Root_Kit is a subClass from Downloaders","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Stealth_Virus is a subClass from Virus","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Logic_Bomb is a subClass from Virus","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Backdoor","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Torjan_Horse is a subClass from Backdoor","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Flooders","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Auto_Rooter is a subClass from Flooders","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Extended_Star","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Distributed_Star is a subClass from Extended_Star","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from SNMPv3","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"SNMPv2 is a subClass from SNMPv3","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from ","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":" is a subClass from ","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Silicon_Photo_Diode is a subClass from Infrared","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Satellites is a subClass from Infrared","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Microwave","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"IEEE_802.11 is a subClass from Microwave","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Traffic_Analysis","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Release_of_Message_Content is a subClass from Traffic_Analysis","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Idle_Scan","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Wiretapping is a subClass from Idle_Scan","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Gnutella","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"STUN is a subClass from Gnutella","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from BACnet","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"RADIUS is a subClass from BACnet","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Advance_Direct_Connect","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"DHCP is a subClass from Advance_Direct_Connect","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SNMPv1 is a subClass from SNMP","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"BOOTP is a subClass from SNMP","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SNTP is a subClass from NTP","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"NetBIOS is a subClass from NTP","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from RTSP","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"SIP is a subClass from RTSP","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Transparent_Bridge","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Translation_Bridge is a subClass from Transparent_Bridge","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Source_Route_Bridge","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Multiport_Bridge is a subClass from Source_Route_Bridge","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Stateful_Inspection_Forward","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Service_control is a subClass from Stateful_Inspection_Forward","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from User_control","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Bastion_Host is a subClass from User_control","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Negative_Filter is a subClass from Packet_Fittering_Routers","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Single_Homed_Bastion is a subClass from Packet_Fittering_Routers","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Screened_Host_Firewall","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Application_Level_Gateway is a subClass from Screened_Host_Firewall","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Behaviour_control","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Circuit_Level_Gateway is a subClass from Behaviour_control","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Token_Ring","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Frames is a subClass from Token_Ring","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from ","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"BASEF is a subClass from ","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"BASET is a subClass from Gigabit_Ethernet","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"CD is a subClass from Gigabit_Ethernet","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from BASE5","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"BASEFX is a subClass from BASE5","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from VG-Any_LAN","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"BASE2 is a subClass from VG-Any_LAN","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from BASET2","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"BASET4 is a subClass from BASET2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Xerox_PARC","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"BASETX is a subClass from Xerox_PARC","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"IAX is a subClass from VOIP","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"eMail is a subClass from VOIP","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Internet_Society","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"IETF is a subClass from Internet_Society","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from IRTF","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"RFC is a subClass from IRTF","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from ARPANET","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"G is a subClass from ARPANET","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from G","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"World_Wide_Web is a subClass from G","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from IAB","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"G is a subClass from IAB","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from IP","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"IPTV is a subClass from IP","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Extreme_Network is a subClass from ExtremeXOS","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"ZyNOS is a subClass from ExtremeXOS","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Huawei is a subClass from VRP","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"CISCO_IOS is a subClass from VRP","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Jupiter_Networks is a subClass from JUNOS","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"MOS is a subClass from JUNOS","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Skype_Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"SDP is a subClass from Skype_Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from SVOIP","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"RTP is a subClass from SVOIP","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from MGCP","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"SIP is a subClass from MGCP","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from H.323","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"IAX is a subClass from H.323","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Partially_Connected","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Fully_Connected is a subClass from Partially_Connected","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Native","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Detection_Specific is a subClass from Native","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Routing","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Packet is a subClass from Routing","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Logical_Addressing","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Forwarding is a subClass from Logical_Addressing","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Spatial_OAM","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"TDM is a subClass from Spatial_OAM","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from SDM","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"WDM is a subClass from SDM","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Service_Point_Addressing","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Segmentation_and_Reassembly is a subClass from Service_Point_Addressing","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Flow_Control","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Error_Control is a subClass from Flow_Control","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Datagrams","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Connection_Control is a subClass from Datagrams","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from IANA","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Transmission_Control_Protocol is a subClass from IANA","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Packet","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"User_Datagram_Protocol is a subClass from Packet","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Internet_Protocol_Version_6","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Connectionless_Service is a subClass from Internet_Protocol_Version_6","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from SSTP","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"SSH is a subClass from SSTP","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from TLS","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Intranet_VPN is a subClass from TLS","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from MPPE","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Tunnelling is a subClass from MPPE","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Extranet_VPN","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"PPP is a subClass from Extranet_VPN","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from L2TP","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"DTLS is a subClass from L2TP","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Remote_access_VPN","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"IPSec is a subClass from Remote_access_VPN","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Advance_Direct_Connect","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Apple_Filing_Protocol is a subClass from Advance_Direct_Connect","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from DHCP","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"RDP is a subClass from DHCP","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from NAT","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"POP is a subClass from NAT","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from HTTP","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"NNTP is a subClass from HTTP","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from r_login","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"SMTP is a subClass from r_login","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from DNS","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"DICT is a subClass from DNS","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from NetBIOS","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Connection_Oriented_Service is a subClass from NetBIOS","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Internet_Relay_Chat","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Finger_protocol is a subClass from Internet_Relay_Chat","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Telnet","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"TFTP is a subClass from Telnet","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"IMAP2 is a subClass from IMAP","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Bit_Torrent is a subClass from IMAP","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from HTTPS","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"BACnet is a subClass from HTTPS","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from BOOTP","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"PPP is a subClass from BOOTP","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from RIP","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"r_sync is a subClass from RIP","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from SIP","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"SSH is a subClass from SIP","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from FTP","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"SNMP is a subClass from FTP","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from RTSP","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Gopher_Protocol is a subClass from RTSP","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from SOAP","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"LDAP is a subClass from SOAP","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Coaxial_Cable is a subClass from Guided_Media","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Wireless is a subClass from Guided_Media","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Pure_Honeypots is a subClass from Honeypots","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Rule_Based_Detection is a subClass from Honeypots","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Anomaly_Detection","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Host_Based_IDS is a subClass from Anomaly_Detection","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Application_Based_IDS","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Audit_Record is a subClass from Application_Based_IDS","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Network_Based_IDS","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Statistical_Anomaly_Detection is a subClass from Network_Based_IDS","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Misuse_Detection","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Target_Based_IDS is a subClass from Misuse_Detection","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Storage_Area_Network","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Home_Area_Network is a subClass from Storage_Area_Network","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Windows_for_Workgroup","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Apple_Share is a subClass from Windows_for_Workgroup","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from SMB","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"SOCKS is a subClass from SMB","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from P","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Synchronization is a subClass from P","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from NFS","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Dialog_Control is a subClass from NFS","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Radio_Repeaters","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Optical_Repeaters is a subClass from Radio_Repeaters","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from IDEA","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Blowfish is a subClass from IDEA","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from RC5","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"DES is a subClass from RC5","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"X is a subClass from BASEX","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"BASET is a subClass from BASEX","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Zero_Day_Exploit","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Ultrafast_Spreading is a subClass from Zero_Day_Exploit","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Transport_Vehicles","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Polymorphic is a subClass from Transport_Vehicles","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Multiplatform","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Multi_Exploit is a subClass from Multiplatform","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Linear_Bus","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Distributed_Bus is a subClass from Linear_Bus","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Windows_2012","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Windows_2008 is a subClass from Windows_2012","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Windows_2003","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Windows_2000 is a subClass from Windows_2003","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Class_Fa","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Class_F is a subClass from Class_Fa","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Positive_Filter","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Negative_Filter is a subClass from Positive_Filter","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from RSA","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"IES is a subClass from RSA","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Variable_Bit_Rate is a subClass from ","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Type_5 is a subClass from ","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"VBR-RT is a subClass from Type_2","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Type_1 is a subClass from Type_2","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from STS-768","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"STS-48 is a subClass from STS-768","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from STS-192","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Unidirectional_Path_Switching_Ring is a subClass from STS-192","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Bidirectional_Path_Switching_Ring","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"STS-24 is a subClass from Bidirectional_Path_Switching_Ring","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from STS-12","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Linear_Automatic_Protection_Switching is a subClass from STS-12","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from STS-3","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"STS-1 is a subClass from STS-3","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"STS-1 is a subClass from SDH","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Internet_Protocol is a subClass from SDH","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"BASET is a subClass from Ethernet","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"ATM is a subClass from Ethernet","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"MC-SS is a subClass from Statistical_Multiplexing","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Circuit_Mode is a subClass from Statistical_Multiplexing","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Extranet is a subClass from Scope","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Protocol is a subClass from Scope","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Interception is a subClass from Security","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Networking_Hardware is a subClass from Security","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Application_Layer is a subClass from IP_Suite","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Topology is a subClass from IP_Suite","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Congession is a subClass from Performance","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Network_Operating_System is a subClass from Performance","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Backbone_Network is a subClass from Scale","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"OSI_Model is a subClass from Scale","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"RC4 is a subClass from Stream_Cipher","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Block_Cipher is a subClass from Stream_Cipher","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Yahoo_Mail","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Hotmail is a subClass from Yahoo_Mail","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Molniya","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Low_Earth_Orbit is a subClass from Molniya","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Geostationary","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Elliptical is a subClass from Geostationary","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Wide_Area_Network","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Personal_Area_Network is a subClass from Wide_Area_Network","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Metropolitan_Area_Network","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Local_Area_Network is a subClass from Metropolitan_Area_Network","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Campus_Area_Network","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Backbone_Network is a subClass from Campus_Area_Network","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from RG6","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Radio_Frequency_Signals is a subClass from RG6","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Hardline","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Biaxial is a subClass from Hardline","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Rigid_Line","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Oliver_Heaviside is a subClass from Rigid_Line","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Radiating","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Triaxial is a subClass from Radiating","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Semirigid","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Twinaxial is a subClass from Semirigid","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from SSH.2","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"SFTP is a subClass from SSH.2","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from POP3","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"POP2 is a subClass from POP3","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Windows_2000 is a subClass from Windows_Server","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Novel_Netware is a subClass from Windows_Server","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Video_on_Demand","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Time_Shifted_TV is a subClass from Video_on_Demand","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Cut_Through","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Access_Switch is a subClass from Cut_Through","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Data_Center_Switches is a subClass from Core_Switch","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Fragment_Free is a subClass from Core_Switch","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Virtual_Networking is a subClass from Distribution_Switch","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Adaptive_Switching is a subClass from Distribution_Switch","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from THSS","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Multiplexing is a subClass from THSS","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from CSS","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Analog_Modulation is a subClass from CSS","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from HMAC","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"CMAC is a subClass from HMAC","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Elliptic_Curve_Cryptography is a subClass from Public_Key_Encryption","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Hash_and_Mac_Algebra is a subClass from Public_Key_Encryption","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Interruption","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Integrity is a subClass from Interruption","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Public_Key_Cryptography is a subClass from Cryptography","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Symmetrie_Encryption is a subClass from Cryptography","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Firewall is a subClass from System_Security","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Fabrication is a subClass from System_Security","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Confidentiality","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Modification is a subClass from Confidentiality","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Spammer_Programs is a subClass from Malicious_Software","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Passive_Attacks is a subClass from Malicious_Software","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Replay is a subClass from Active_Attacks","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Availablity is a subClass from Active_Attacks","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Loaded_TP is a subClass from Twisted_Pair","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Optical_Fibre is a subClass from Twisted_Pair","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Class_F is a subClass from Shielded_Foiled_Twisted_Pair","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Bonded_TP is a subClass from Shielded_Foiled_Twisted_Pair","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Twisted_Ribbon_Cable","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Screened_Twisted_Pair is a subClass from Twisted_Ribbon_Cable","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Shielded_Twisted_Pair","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Screened_Shielded_Twisted_Pair is a subClass from Shielded_Twisted_Pair","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Cat3 is a subClass from Unshielded_Twisted_Pain","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Loaded_TP is a subClass from Unshielded_Twisted_Pain","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Wifi_Repeater","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"LAN_Repeater is a subClass from Wifi_Repeater","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Logical_Link_Control_Sublayer","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Flow_Control is a subClass from Logical_Link_Control_Sublayer","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Error_Control","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Frames is a subClass from Error_Control","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Physical_Addressing","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Media_Access_Control is a subClass from Physical_Addressing","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Framing","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Access_Control is a subClass from Framing","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Active_Hub is a subClass from Hub","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Modem is a subClass from Hub","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"MAC_Address is a subClass from Bridge","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Brouter is a subClass from Bridge","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Routing_table is a subClass from Router","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Repeater is a subClass from Router","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Archived_Gateway is a subClass from Gateway","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Switch is a subClass from Gateway","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from SC-FDM","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Dynamic_TDM is a subClass from SC-FDM","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from OFDMA","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Packet_Mode is a subClass from OFDMA","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from DSSS","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"FHSS is a subClass from DSSS","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Translation","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Encryption is a subClass from Translation","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Direct_DS","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Arbitrated_DS is a subClass from Direct_DS","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Active_Optical_Network","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"FTTX is a subClass from Active_Optical_Network","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Single_Mode_Fiber","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Direct_Fiber is a subClass from Single_Mode_Fiber","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Passive_Optical_Network","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Plastics is a subClass from Passive_Optical_Network","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Shared_Fiber","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Multimode_Fiber is a subClass from Shared_Fiber","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Cat6","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Cat5 is a subClass from Cat6","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Cat4","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Cat3 is a subClass from Cat4","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Unidirectional_Gateway","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Synchronazation_Gateway is a subClass from Unidirectional_Gateway","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Bidirectional_Gateway","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Archived_Gateway is a subClass from Bidirectional_Gateway","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Socket_Address is a subClass from Transport_Layer","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Network_Interface is a subClass from Transport_Layer","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"IP_Address is a subClass from Internet_Layer","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Application_Layer is a subClass from Internet_Layer","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from FTTH","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"FTTB is a subClass from FTTH","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from FTTD","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"FTTC is a subClass from FTTD","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from FTTN","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"FTTP is a subClass from FTTN","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from ASP","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Mozilla_Firefox is a subClass from ASP","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Safari","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"HTTP is a subClass from Safari","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from JSP","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"URI is a subClass from JSP","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Facebook","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"HTML is a subClass from Facebook","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Internet_Explorer","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Twitter is a subClass from Internet_Explorer","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Opera","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Google is a subClass from Opera","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Youtube","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Google_Chrome is a subClass from Youtube","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Bing","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":" is a subClass from Bing","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from URL","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"PHP is a subClass from URL","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from High_Interaction_Honeypots","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Production_Honeypots is a subClass from High_Interaction_Honeypots","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Low_Interaction_Honeypots","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Research_Honeypots is a subClass from Low_Interaction_Honeypots","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Error_Rate","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Bandwidth is a subClass from Error_Rate","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Latency","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Jitter is a subClass from Latency","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Throughput","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Interplay_Factors is a subClass from Throughput","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Parasitic_Virus","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Memory_Resident_Virus is a subClass from Parasitic_Virus","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Polymorphic_Virus","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Metamorphic_Virus is a subClass from Polymorphic_Virus","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Boot_Sector_Virus","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Stealth_Virus is a subClass from Boot_Sector_Virus","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Orginal_IMAP","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"IMAP4 is a subClass from Orginal_IMAP","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from IMAP2bis","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"IMAP3 is a subClass from IMAP2bis","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Class_E","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Class_D is a subClass from Class_E","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Class_C","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Class_B is a subClass from Class_C","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from _ad","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"_g is a subClass from _ad","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from ","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":" is a subClass from ","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from _b","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"_ac is a subClass from _b","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from ","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"_a_OFDM_Waveform is a subClass from ","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Ethernet_Hub","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Repeater_Hub is a subClass from Ethernet_Hub","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Network_Hub","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Multiport_Hub is a subClass from Network_Hub","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from VPN","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Firewall is a subClass from VPN","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Novel_Netware is a subClass from Server","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Router_Operating_System is a subClass from Server","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Intranet","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Internet is a subClass from Intranet","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Core_Router","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Distance_Vector_Routing is a subClass from Core_Router","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Static_Routing","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Inter_Provider_Border_Router is a subClass from Static_Routing","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Wireless_Router","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Dynamic_Routing is a subClass from Wireless_Router","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Subscriber_Edge_Router","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Link_State_Routing is a subClass from Subscriber_Edge_Router","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Broad_Band_Router","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Edge_Router is a subClass from Broad_Band_Router","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Circuit_Switching is a subClass from Switched","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Permanent is a subClass from Switched","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from AM","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"SM is a subClass from AM","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from QAM","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"PM is a subClass from QAM","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from SSB","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"FM is a subClass from SSB","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Buffer_Overflow","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Smurf_Attack is a subClass from Buffer_Overflow","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Heap_Overflow","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Modification_of_Message is a subClass from Heap_Overflow","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Cyber_Attack","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"DOS is a subClass from Cyber_Attack","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from ARP_Poisoning","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"SQL_Injection is a subClass from ARP_Poisoning","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Masquerade","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Spoofing is a subClass from Masquerade","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Format_String_Attack","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Replay is a subClass from Format_String_Attack","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"ATM is a subClass from Packet_Switching","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Circuit_Switching is a subClass from Packet_Switching","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Physical_Layer","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Management_Plane is a subClass from Physical_Layer","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Virtual_Circuit is a subClass from Virtual_Path","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"User_Plane is a subClass from Virtual_Path","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Higher_Layer_Protocols","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"ATM_Layer is a subClass from Higher_Layer_Protocols","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Control_Plane","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Cells is a subClass from Control_Plane","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Voice","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"AAL is a subClass from Voice","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"null is a subClass from Data","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Video is a subClass from Data","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which one of the following response pairs are related ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Application\tuses\tRADIUS","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Network\tuses\tRADIUS","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"ISO_Standard\tuses\tRADIUS","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Data_Link\tuses\tRADIUS","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which one of the following response pairs are related ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Internet_Society\tcommittee\tIAB","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"eMail\tcommittee\tIAB","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"VOIP\tcommittee\tIAB","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"RFC\tcommittee\tIAB","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"property"}]